Guide to the Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, Records SC0650
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, records
1973-1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Centro Chicano
SC0650
6.5 Linear Feet
Records pertaining to the administration of the center and its programs.
Scope and Content of Collection
These records, dating from 1973 to 1991, include correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, calendars, publications, budget files, program files, clippings, articles, and other materials pertaining to the administration of the center and its programs. Other student groups represented in the collection include MEChA, the Chicano Pre-Medical Organization, Casa Zapata (theme dorm), and the publication LA ONDA.
Biography / Administrative History
The mission statement of El Centro Chicano as adopted by the Guiding Concilio in 1991 is "to catalyze Chicanos and Latinos at Stanford into a proactive community that creates an environment which celebrates and promotes the history, contributions, intellectual heritage, education, growth, and empowerment of all Chicanos and Latinos here and beyond." El Centro sponsors programs in leadership development, academic support, cultural events, and social activities.
Acquisition Information
Administrative transfer, 2002.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Mexican Americans -- Education.; Mexican Americans -- Social conditions; Mexican Americans -- Students; Stanford University. Centro Chicano; Stanford University. Casa Zapata
- Records, Series 1
  - Justice for Carlos Montes (Paper), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Funding Sources (Misc) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - KZSU - relevant materials (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - M.E.Ch.A. (Misc. info.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Voz de la Gente - Record Co. Labels (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - La Onda - minutes and funding proposal, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Women's Health Services sources for Raza Health Education Network, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CHE (Chicanos in Health Education) - Cinco de Mayo Proposal, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Chicano Pre-meds, 1973-76 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - three contact sheets (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - MEChA Workstudy Manual, (1978-83) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CHE, 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chicano Pre/Medical Organization (includes copy of MEChA Workstudy Manual), 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer Jobs Info, 1979-81 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Medicina y la Mujer - conference materials, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - HCOP (Health Professions Career Opportunity Program) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chicano Pre-Med/Pre-Health Students - letterhead (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - MALDEF newsletter, Winter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - La Onda articles (typescripts), including interview with President Don Kennedy Dec., 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Health Fair, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford/PMAA Conference Committee - agenda, April 5, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Voz de la Gente - Playlists, 1979-82 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chicano music, miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - La RaMA (la raza medical association) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - La RaMA #2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Summer Health Programs for Minority Students, 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Health Careers Network Newsletter, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Area Publicity: sources and examples (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Roster, Chicano Pre-Med/Pre-Health Organization, 1980-81 (includes Chicano Pre-Med Survey (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Roster, Chicano Pre-Med/Pre-Health Organization, 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1980-81 Harvest Day Flyer (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Medical School Contact Sheet (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MEChA/CHE ideology (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Issues of La Onda (SU publication) and La Gente (UCLA publication), May, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chicano Graduation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Centro Cultural," Carlos Moreno (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Account forms and handbook (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chicano Nat'l Review, 7/78-2/79 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chicano Nat'l Review, May '79 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings [Stanford Daily Magazine Nov. 29, 1979: Stanford in the 1970s], 1979-80 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chicano Nat'l Review, April 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - La Onda Mailing List (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chicano Community Newsletter (Chicano Affairs Office), Vol. 1 No. 1-3, 1976-77 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - La Onda, articles and miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Posters and notices (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Copies of La Onda (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Copies of La Onda (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Typesetting receipts-La Onda (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - La Onda Finances (ASSU) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Budget and Administration Committee Minutes, 1984-85 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budget and Administration, (1984-85) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1984-85 Centro Annual Report (orig.) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board Orientations, 1981-84 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board Members Rosters, 1979-84 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Call for Members, 1982-83 and 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board Minutes, 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Programs and Proposals, 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Budget Committee Information, 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board Minutes, 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board Members Year End Reports, 1982-83 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Budget Committee info, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board Minutes, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board Minutes, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Budget Committee Info., 1980-81 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Budget Committee Info., 1981-82 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Concilio de Asuntos Chicanos, minutes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Interim Policy Board (Winter Qtr. 1978) Chicano Cultural and Activities Center (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - DOSA Staff Meetings Sylvia meetings and memos, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Funding Committee Info, 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Funding Committee Info, 1981082 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Funding Committee Info, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Funding Committee Info, 1979-80 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, Michael Perez and others, 1977-84 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Administration Committee, 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Budget and Administration, 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Daily, 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Administration (Furniture), 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Policies, 1988-89 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chron, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chron Incoming, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Space Survey, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - El Centro Annual Report, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Centro Brochure, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Centro Forms, 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chron (outgoing), 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chron (incoming), 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Staffing Committee Info., 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Staffing Committee info., 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chicano Population Census Statistics, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Year-End Reports, 1979-80 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Staffing Committee info., 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Office Coordinator position info, (pre 1984/85) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Staffing Committee info., 1979-80 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - DOSA [Dean of Student Affairs] information (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Student Activities Resource manual (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - La Raza Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Year end reports, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - General programs and Proposals, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Interns' Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaires (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - CSAC Staff meeting minutes, plans and assignments, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Interns' Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Funding sources (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) programs, 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Budget Committee Information, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) Budget Info, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) Budget, 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CSAC Budget, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - El Centro Transition Team, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Search for El Centro Dean, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ramirez memo Re: Chicano Community Controversy, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - INDA Interim Governance Proposal, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Search Committee Announcements Mailing list, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Search Committee originals (minutes, agenda) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arroyo, Luis L. Observations on the Chicano Fellows Program and the Undergraduate Program on Mexican Culture and Society in the United States, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mission Mural walk maps (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bible Sheets (re building facilities), 1971-84 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual Asbestos notification, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Wheel Chair Ramp, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Brochure, 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - El Centro Chicano, 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Logos, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Organization Account Numbers, 1986-87 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Recycling Services, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Centro Improvement, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Keys (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Stationery Letterhead Original (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Centro Stationery (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Damages in building (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Risk management, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Centro Structure Chart, 1984-86 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Recycling Center, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Computer Equipment Inventory, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Annual Asbestos Notification, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Building Energy Reports, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Facilities Information, 1979-84 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Facilities Inventory, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Gandalf Circuit, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Admissions Space Request, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Spring 1985 Office Inventory (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Montoya Mural Project, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Lounge Mural, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Centro Office Mural Project, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - El Centro Fall Staff Retreat, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - El Centro Winter Staff Retreat, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - El Centro Spring Staff Retreat, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Indirect Cost Rates, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Lounge and Conference calendar (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Facilities Calendar, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 1987-88 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, 1984-85 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Administration and Planning Committee, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Centro Staff, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chicano Community Retreat, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Centro Summer Planning/Work, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - El Centro program Advisor, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Daily contract, 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Student Organization Loan Policy, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Budget and Administration, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1985-86 FY Closing (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - DOSA new Staff orientation, Jan. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - M. Jackson Orientation (FM), 12/20/89 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - For the New Dean: Your Info File (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - D. Kennedy, Stanford In Its Second Century, April 5, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Campus Affairs Retreat 8/23/90 (includes James W. Lyons, "Functions of Student Affairs at Stanford,", 1989) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Centro Five Year Plan, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Stamp [Student Alumni Mentor Program]-Larry Green, June 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Computer Class Email, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Computer Class PRISM, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Wylbur Documents, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Irvine Foundation, grant proposal, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ho Fund, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CAAG [Campus Affairs Administrative Group], 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Grad Students - funding sources (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs Three-Year Plan, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Campus Affairs Three-Year Plan, 1990-93 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Work Study Notes, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - An Analysis of the Computer Environment of El Centro Chicano, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - CPPC Review Process, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Statements, 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Summaries Budget, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Budgets-Res Ed, CPPC, Cowell, 1990-92 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - P. Castaneda presentation, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - P. Castaneda, Feb. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - P. Castaneda Expert Partners, March 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - P. Castaneda Immersion Summer Program, June 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Office move, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - El Centro Fund Account, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Budget, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - CLOC [Chicano/Latino Orientation Committee] Mary Haynes, Feb. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Literacy Project Budget, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Repositioning Steering Committee, March 1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Haas Center, 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Posters for Jing Lyman Lecture Series, Spring, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - El Centro Facilities Use, 1988-89 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Budget Statement, 1989-90 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Winter, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Spring, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Winter, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report-El Centro, 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CGSA, 1989-90 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Staff Retreat, Jan. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - J. Porras Article (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Jing Lyman lecture series, panel "personal reflections by Chicana women at Stanford", May 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - La Raza Staff Association, Jan. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - El Centro Staff meetings Winter, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Funding Sources Leti, April 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Theatre Ideas, April 1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gloria Anzaldua, March 1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Papers in Higher Ed (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - J. Martinez, you can make a difference conference, Jan. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - CPPC, Steve Phillips, Feb. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Latino Issues Forum, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Media Center, Meyer Lib, Mar. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Ethnic American Studies, Meyer Lib., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hispanic Leadership Opportunity Program, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Misc., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - UCMI Student Data (senior survey), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Health promotion program, 1992-93 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Health promotion program #2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Floricanto proposal, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Approaching Stanford, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Assistant Dean/Undergraduate Admission Advising Group, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - BCSC Funding Priorities, May 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CON Courses Summer, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - CPPC Mtg. Advisory Group, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ballet Folklorico Annual Concierto, May 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - California Tomorrow, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Burciaga Article, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CA State Personnel Office, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Chicano/Latino Youth Leadership Project, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - COFHE [Consortium on Financing Higher Education], 1990 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - College Register, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Ethnic and Racial Relations, San Antonio, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Danzy Senna: Unity Editor Disputes, June 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Margaret Ann Fidler Storage Request, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - El Centro Chicano's Dorm reps, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Financial Aid workshop, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Staff Directory verification classified section, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Garcia, Robert, Paper on Mexican American family, March 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Guidelines for use of Centro (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - G. Hernandez Open Letter to S.U., June 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Kathleen Hirooka, 1990/91 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hispanic Business, 1990/91 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hispanic Magazine, 1990/91 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - IDRA [International Development Research Association] newsletter, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Mex Am Research Collection, Feb. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Motivated to Serve Spring Course, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - MLK Tresidder Multicultural Tea, Jan. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Office of Multicultural Development, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Parking, 1990-91 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Placement services for laid off Stanford employees, June 1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Politzer March 16, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Readings, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Refugee Service Center in America, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - UC Mexus Conf., Sept. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - The Urban Institute, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - PMAA, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - SACNAS news, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SCANN, May 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - SCCR Publications, July 1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Center for the Study of Families, Youth and Children, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Orientation, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Powwow - program, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Student Telethon, May 14, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Interviews, Oct. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) proposals and proposals, 1979-80 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) proposals and proposals, 1980-81 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) proposals and proposals, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Centro Organizations and Rosters (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - CSAC (El Centro Chicano) Descriptions and year end reports, 1980-83 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Casa Zapata (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Casa Zapata (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - CPPC James Patterson, Feb. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Mex Amer Folk remedies, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Multiracial theme house, March 1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Inst. For International Studies, Jan. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Jesse Unruh Fellowship Program, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - CSAC, April 1990 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Celebration for Stanford Workers, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - El Centro program board (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - L. Brianin-Latiro Health practices, Oct. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chacon, M. et al, Chicanas in post secondary education, July 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Citibank, J. March fundraising, May 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Community Service Hours, Dec. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - H. Cuevas, UAS, Jan. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Henry Cisneros visit, May, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - MEChA Budget, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - MESA, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Tresidder, Mar. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - SSp ARC, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Young Alumnai/I Brainstorming group, Mar. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dorm Reps List, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - RA Training, 1990-91 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Weekly Schedule-El Centro Staff, Jan. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-El Centro Staff, Jan. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - El Centro Study nights Schedule, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - FM-Welcome letter to students Dec. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - DOSA letters of appreciation Charlene Aguilar (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Letters-Retreat 2/90 Fernando de Necochea (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Rachel Moran, law school letter, Mar. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - DOSA-CSMS, Mar. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Campus Affairs Admin group (M. Jackson), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Student Affairs Council Meeting dates, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Greg Ricks, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Cole, Sarah, Dir. Of Research - campus affairs 1/2/90 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-082
  - Academic Planning Office, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assistant Dean of Students, 1971-74 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admission Policy and Procedures, 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Assistant Director of Admissions, 1970-73 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Students, 1971-73 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Assistant Dean of Student Affairs – position proposal, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Admissions, 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Graduate Studies, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Undergraduate Studies, Annual Report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Assistant Dean of Students Affairs Position Search Committee 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights: U. S. Commission 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cabinet Committee on Opportunities for the Spanish Speaking, 1970-73 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Department of Human Resources Development: Los Angeles, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ALVISO (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The ALVISO Economic Development Area, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Associations: American College Public Relations Association (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Associations: American Political Science Association (Chicano Caucus) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Associations: Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Associations: Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Associations: Council for Opportunity in Graduate Management Education (COGME) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Associations: Mex-Am Political Association (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Associations: National Economical Development Association (NEDA) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bing Nursery, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Blacks – information (re office of Asst. to President for Black Affairs), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Assistant to the President – Mayates, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees, 1968-70 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bibliography Reviews (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Book Reviews (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence re publications, 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Budget Committee (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Career Placement and Planning (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Census Publications (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Taskforce Committee (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chicano Concerns Task Force, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Taskforce on Chicanos, U. C., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Chicano Studies, 1968-73 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Chicano Faculty File (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Miquiztle 1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chicanas – information (conference at S.U.), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Chicano Social Scientists (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Zapata Spring Lecture Series 1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Humanities and Sciences Students Association (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Chicano Education Association 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1971-73 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Chicano Law Student Association 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Chicano Alumni (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Chicano Pre-Law Students (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Chicano Pre-Med Students (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - School of Medicine Pre-Med Summer Program 1972 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - School of Medicine Pre-Med Program 1973 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Freshmen Orientation 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Chicano Graduate Students Autumn 1973 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Children's Center - Stanford University, 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Committee on Committees of the Faculty Senate, 1970-72 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Committee of Fifteen 1972 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Committee on Minority Affairs (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Admission and Financial Aid (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Behavioral Science Sub-Committee on Human Subjects, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Committees (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Transfer Cooperative Committee, Jr. College Students, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Committees – various (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Coalition for an Academic Community (Box 1, Folder 63)